{
  "level": 4,
  "unit": 3,
  "spelling": [
    {
      "week": "1",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "This _____________ will flavor the sauce.",
          "answer": "herb"
        },
        { "prompt": "A _____________ ran by the window.", "answer": "person" },
        { "prompt": "I lectured my dog _____________ .", "answer": "sternly" },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ slithered past my feet.",
          "answer": "serpent"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The fall could have been _____________ .",
          "answer": "worse"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "There was a _____________ in the oyster.",
          "answer": "pearl"
        },
        { "prompt": "My keyboard was _____________ .", "answer": "dirty" },
        {
          "prompt": "Our cat gave _____________ to eight kittens.",
          "answer": "birth"
        },
        { "prompt": "Only his _____________ was torn.", "answer": "shirt" },
        {
          "prompt": "I _____________ my hair around my finger.",
          "answer": "twirl"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ the soapy water in the glass.",
          "answer": "swirl"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "She bought a new leather _____________ .",
          "answer": "purse"
        },
        { "prompt": "Her hair had a little _____________ .", "answer": "curl" },
        { "prompt": "The car rounded the _____________ .", "answer": "curve" },
        { "prompt": "He fell off the _____________ .", "answer": "curb" },
        {
          "prompt": "The quarterback can _____________ the football.",
          "answer": "hurl"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We have _____________ on Thanksgiving.",
          "answer": "turkey"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ came from our garden.",
          "answer": "turnip"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I stated the _____________ of my visit.",
          "answer": "purpose"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The writing _____________ from the rain.",
          "answer": "blurred"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "2",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Try not to _____________ your shirt.",
          "answer": "wrinkle"
        },
        { "prompt": "Don’t _____________ in your chair.", "answer": "wriggle" },
        {
          "prompt": "Throw away the candy _____________ .",
          "answer": "wrapper"
        },
        { "prompt": "The toolbox had a _____________ .", "answer": "wrench" },
        {
          "prompt": "Can you _____________ that question?",
          "answer": "answer"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The baker will _____________ the dough.",
          "answer": "knead"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We used _____________ to cut the meat.",
          "answer": "knives"
        },
        { "prompt": "What are you _____________ for?", "answer": "known" },
        {
          "prompt": "He had to _____________ to see what was under the couch.",
          "answer": "kneel"
        },
        { "prompt": "Only Nate _____________ the secret.", "answer": "knew" },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ came to fix the pipe.",
          "answer": "plumber"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We bought _____________ at the store.",
          "answer": "combs"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Monkeys and people have _____________ .",
          "answer": "thumbs"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "She has many _____________ on her farm.",
          "answer": "lambs"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The building was not safe, so they had to _____________ it.",
          "answer": "condemn"
        },
        { "prompt": "I must _____________ from my job.", "answer": "resign" },
        {
          "prompt": "It’s _____________ that we will win.",
          "answer": "doubtful"
        },
        { "prompt": "The drive took an _____________ .", "answer": "hour" },
        { "prompt": "_____________ is the best policy.", "answer": "honesty" },
        { "prompt": "It was an _____________ to be chosen.", "answer": "honor" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "3",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "What’s in the _____________ of the candy?",
          "answer": "center"
        },
        { "prompt": "We practice _____________ a week.", "answer": "once" },
        {
          "prompt": "I loved the last _____________ of the play.",
          "answer": "scene"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Add a little _____________ to your food.",
          "answer": "spice"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I like the lions in the _____________ .",
          "answer": "circus"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Watch out for that wet _____________ !",
          "answer": "cement"
        },
        { "prompt": "You can trust the _____________ .", "answer": "police" },
        {
          "prompt": "Are you _____________ you saw a bear?",
          "answer": "certain"
        },
        { "prompt": "Add one _____________ of sugar.", "answer": "ounce" },
        { "prompt": "_____________ at the mirror.", "answer": "glance" },
        {
          "prompt": "Wash the _____________ off your hands.",
          "answer": "germs"
        },
        { "prompt": "Let’s cross the _____________ .", "answer": "bridge" },
        {
          "prompt": "I earned a _____________ at the scout meeting.",
          "answer": "badge"
        },
        { "prompt": "That is really _____________ .", "answer": "strange" },
        { "prompt": "Peel the _____________ .", "answer": "orange" },
        {
          "prompt": "Do you like the taste of _____________ ?",
          "answer": "ginger"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I asked, “May I have a _____________ of cheese?”",
          "answer": "wedge"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Please _____________ the books neatly.",
          "answer": "arrange"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Use a _____________ to wash the table.",
          "answer": "sponge"
        },
        { "prompt": "In which _____________ do you live?", "answer": "village" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "4",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "_____________ live in the mud.", "answer": "clams" },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ have a refreshing taste!",
          "answer": "mints"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Jenna made _____________ for the play.",
          "answer": "props"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "She painted the stone _____________ .",
          "answer": "arches"
        },
        { "prompt": "The actresses wore _____________ .", "answer": "dresses" },
        {
          "prompt": "Your _____________ will love the play!",
          "answer": "parents"
        },
        { "prompt": "Bats often live in _____________ .", "answer": "caves" },
        { "prompt": "Have you seen my _____________ ?", "answer": "glasses" },
        {
          "prompt": "One of her _____________ is knitting.",
          "answer": "hobbies"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The drivers started their _____________ .",
          "answer": "engines"
        },
        { "prompt": "Sit on one of the _____________ .", "answer": "couches" },
        {
          "prompt": "Green _____________ pointed us home.",
          "answer": "arrows"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We were friends, not _____________ .",
          "answer": "enemies"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "There were six _____________ in the nursery.",
          "answer": "babies"
        },
        { "prompt": "Zack visited two _____________ .", "answer": "ranches" },
        {
          "prompt": "Kate sewed _____________ on her jeans.",
          "answer": "patches"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Julio made no _____________ on his test.",
          "answer": "mistakes"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We bought _____________ for our trip.",
          "answer": "supplies"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Some _____________ look like tiny trees.",
          "answer": "mosses"
        },
        { "prompt": "Where did the _____________ fight?", "answer": "armies" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "The cat peered into the _____________ .",
          "answer": "fishbowl"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The fort has a _____________ tower.",
          "answer": "lookout"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Sam drew a line with his _____________ .",
          "answer": "yardstick"
        },
        { "prompt": "Papers lay on the _____________ .", "answer": "desktop" },
        { "prompt": "We cooked over a _____________ .", "answer": "campfire" },
        { "prompt": "He heard thunder _____________ .", "answer": "overhead" },
        {
          "prompt": "Luckily, the tent was _____________ !",
          "answer": "waterproof"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Anna’s _____________ is visiting.",
          "answer": "grandparent"
        },
        { "prompt": "We boarded the _____________ car.", "answer": "railroad" },
        {
          "prompt": "School closed for the _____________ .",
          "answer": "snowstorm"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The principal spoke over the _____________ .",
          "answer": "loudspeaker"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Every shelf of the _____________ is full.",
          "answer": "bookcase"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "David has drums in his _____________ .",
          "answer": "bedroom"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ covered my eyes.",
          "answer": "blindfold"
        },
        { "prompt": "The _____________ mice were tiny.", "answer": "newborn" },
        { "prompt": "We bought a new _____________ .", "answer": "bedspread" },
        {
          "prompt": "Did you build that by _____________ ?",
          "answer": "yourself"
        },
        { "prompt": "Try not to _____________ it.", "answer": "overdo" },
        {
          "prompt": "I hung sheets on a _____________ .",
          "answer": "clothesline"
        },
        { "prompt": "Let’s _____________ the journey.", "answer": "undertake" }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
